Hello friends, ICC Bank's WhatsApp
number is 6400 860. Save this number
on your WhatsApp and through it
you can check your account balance,
check your last date,
block or unlock your card, cancel an FD,
pay your bills, and
avail of numerous other features. Friends,
for this it is important that your registered number
works with WhatsApp. Only then can you make the necessary changes.
We have
saved the number on WhatsApp here. Now we have to
type "hi" here and see that
WhatsApp will show the banking services option here. The
first option is for branch
banking services. From here you can see the balance
inquiry history, credit card account details,
and many other
features are available here. So let's
show you how to do a balance inquiry.
First, we will type "one" and see that the
option to check account balance is showing here. Then
again we have to type "open" here
and see that our balance is showing here. So
friends, this is how you
can check your balance here. If you liked this video, please
like it and
subscribe to our channel.  do it a